hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft
although you might not recognize where i
am
because we're in a very very strange
forest
we did a live stream
recently
raising money for charity and everyone
who donated over a certain amount got a
tree whether it was a custom tree a
small tree a big tree and
as you can see
it was incredibly successful in two
hours iskal and i raised over 39 000
for this charity
and fortunately i actually time lapsed
the whole thing
so take a look at this all of these will
be in the map
forever and each tree has someone's name
on it the charity is love tropics in
conjunction with cool earth and the
money raised will be going to help a
village in papua new guinea
this is directly to protect the
environment from climate change and the
impact of deforestation it's so so cool
thank you anyone and everyone who
supported and donated at the live stream
and hopefully we can do more things like
this in the future because this forest
is absolutely insane and a huge thank
you to the guys on love tropics who sat
for hours even after the live stream had
finished planting and naming every
single one of these trees
so after many hours of planting and
building trees and labeling them all
we're gonna have to leave this area but
it is a monument to what we can do to
save the planet and there's a tree with
a thumbs up
there's all sorts of weird and wonderful
trees iron and emerald blocks poultry
man i don't know who that is anyway
let's head back to the main island where
we're going to continue with our
hermitcraft journey
the timer is still ticking on this
hourglass and i've actually found out
what this is about uh some of you guys
said in the comments this is the
countdown to when cherry which is uh
scars shop over here it's the countdown
to when it reopens because as you can
see here it's closed for refurbishment
which means no one can get their hands
on the redstone stuff they need you know
maybe sahara here should capitalize on
that with cherry out of business for a
while
we could definitely
oh wait we totally already stock a load
of redstone stuff never mind don't even
know my own stock but one thing that
we're missing is gravel but we haven't
actually sold out of things recently i
guess the shopping district is a little
bit stale at the moment but what we
really need to do is get our hands on a
bunch of gravel and sand because pretty
much every single project i'm going to
be working on
is made out of concrete it seems to be a
never ending cycle so
time for me solo to go and grab some
gravel and some sand and a little time
lapse for you let's go i mean it's not
really exciting is it it's literally
just me mining some sand and equally
mining some gravel but there's something
incredibly satisfying about the time
lapse like this i don't know what it is
so we got our hands on the sand and the
gravel
and now iskall's messaged me saying he
wants to meet up but he hasn't exactly
told me why so let's go meet up with
iskaw in the architect room and see what
he wants
why am i here iskal what do we need to
meet you your face dude
yeah i know i know i know it it is what
it is i've upgraded my chair as well
well you think you think you're better
than me
with your iron blocks and your your more
expensive blocks yours is clearly still
taller
now the reason i have somebody here
today is because i have built the very
first anti-death contraption in our
bunker because people are dying man so
many people have actually quite a few i
think who cub has died is cub dead as
well oh my goodness yeah
i know i know red dog stress dog
uh exuma void cub fan and scar and scar
too many too many of our friends two men
too many have fallen how do we know this
hasn't been trapped i've already been
down here today
but that that is a good point there's
there is a button here yeah i mean super
scared
i almost went into it before the oh i
saw that i saw that it almost went in i
think it's so scary hold on every time i
use that door
i'm scared
yeah me too
i'm sorry about creating something so
scary you made it made it here
yes so down here what i've done
is on the left
is i've made an architect
machine
yes and the idea is
um that first of all
i've been pretty close dying sometimes
we we're both wearing this gold stuff
yeah i've had a few close calls like
really really close calls
because of that i did some research and
it turns out that glass protection and
every other protection you can multiply
by stacking them on each on each item so
if you have it on your chest plate on
your trousers on your on your boots et
cetera and i have no blast protection
actually i've got a little bit on my
helmet and then
nothing yeah well if you would have four
pieces let's say with blast protection
you take like one heart of damage with
from a tnt blast it's absolutely
insanely op i'll go in first
yep there we go have you got tnt
i got tnt got tmc ready
[Music]
yes
come on
[Laughter]
i should have seen that coming
oh you look away
i wondered why you were messing around
with armor
fantastic
you look fantastic
okay guess we're dragon bros now
oh yes we are
[Laughter]
how did you do that
oh
it's a long process yeah it's a long
process you see the bottom one has the
same border as the rest of this floor
but it's actually a dispenser that had a
dragon head but what about why didn't
the helmet go on me first or did you
remove it no the helmet is still in
there or no the helmet should be in your
inventory but how did it how did it go
how did the dragon get on me first
rather than the helmet because i timed
it with tick-tock
[Laughter]
fair well done well done okay thank you
so there's nothing to do with blast
damage then
no no i'm putting my gold armor back on
i've lost so much protection now
we should go and scare people with this
it's so good although we're not really
scary
walk forward with me
yeah hold on let's walk right there
[Laughter]
have you got more dragon heads
what are you thinking i'm thinking i'm
thinking i'm thinking we could make a
little dragon bro club and we could get
more than more than one of us i mean
this is two out of three architects
right yep we're missing we're missing
and mumbo's not mumbo's not dead so he
could join he could join the dragon bros
oh you've named it okay lol
come on dude
yeah you accepted
okay lol okay
terribly sorry dude
let's set this up to to get mumbo shall
we i think i've got a good idea we've
come over to mumbo's uh witch farm
he's got like a factory going on here at
this point like it's insane it looks
incredible so what i think we could do
we're not really going to just capture
him because he's always wearing his
helmet right
always yeah that's the problem so get
that off we've been we've been
discussing a while and we think the best
way to get him is to wait until mumbo
goes afk up there because he does do
that with all of this factory stuff
going on we've just got to bide our time
wait for him to go afk all the way up
here
because he takes all of his gear off so
that he's safe i don't know who's done
this with the tnt button thing
this is like this is the most tempting
thing i've ever seen in my life
dog presence i really want to impress it
dude
but he takes off all of his weapons and
armor and stuff and puts it in here so
all we got to do is wait for him to go
afk and simply dispense the dragon head
on him
yeah bada bing bada boom that that
should be that should be fully doable as
well he's a dragon bro
do you know what the world i mean we can
always scout
he won't even notice
he when he comes back in the morning
with his morning voice he's like
yeah good morning i've been afk for the
past 12 hour i got kicked after 11 hours
and 30 minutes so it's not been very
successful so let's see what we got
and then he has no idea it's no idea
you know what the best thing is though
we could take his mustache away and he
wouldn't even know
there are a lot of potential
possibilities soon everyone will become
a dragon bro
yeah if they're alive that is
this is genius dude i love this i love
our new little alliance
dragon bros honestly i can't really
believe that i fell for this
but i think we're kind of on to
something here the whole dragon thing
anyone that's alive
i feel like we could get them i actually
found another dragon head just sitting
here on my wall so now i've got two and
here's the best thing that i've found so
far if you put one in your off hand and
one in your other hand it looks like
you're wearing dragon gloves
[Laughter]
this is the stupidest thing i think i've
ever done in hermitcraft but what we're
gonna do is we're gonna get cursive
binding on these we're gonna rename them
and we're going to try and convert as
many people to the dragon bro team
as we can but i'm gonna need some help
for that but i can do this for now quite
easily
dragon bro
mumbo dragon eye so we know who this
one's for
but two really isn't going to cut it
we're gonna need to get a lot more of
these dragon heads if we're gonna
convert everyone into the dragon bro
team it's no longer a live team anymore
this is this is dragon territory so
these are all of the sand and gravel
boxes that i have collected and it's
quite a lot of them i spent a good
amount of time on this and this was
pretty much just so we could get the
concrete machine all filled up
and also i've noticed i take a lot more
damage because i haven't got my gold
helmet anymore i'm really really squishy
like i have actually you for the first
time ended up consuming a totem of
undying which is um
not great
so what i need to do is put this uh in
here and in here so give me a second
this is gonna take a long time to put
together
i'm the only one that actually keeps
this thing stocked up but we actually we
actually need quite a lot of uh concrete
for the next build because i'm going all
in on this dragon bro thing we're gonna
turn the demise bunker that we've made
into
a dragon bro cave so what i'm gonna do
is i'm gonna craft up all the blocks
that i need in order to make a dragon
bro cave which basically means the black
concrete the magenta maybe a bit of pink
as well and then grey for the horns
we're gonna make a giant dragon head
within our bunker
there we go
finally all of this is now loaded up and
while it was going i was also making
concrete at the same time um it wasn't
particularly efficient but i have got
myself a load of black concrete a lot of
magenta and a little bit of light gray
as well i think that's pretty much
everything i need in order to make this
dragon bro head so now we got to go back
to the bunker
and we can start making this thing so in
the bunker i've already got some pillars
here so the dragon head really doesn't
kind of suit this side but
that is relatively untouched so what i
can do
is probably just put a big old dragon
head in here so let's do a quick old
time lapse of me trying to make a dragon
head and i don't know the best way to do
this really
let's take let's take that and i'll use
this as my basis so that i can get it
kind of pixel perfect
all right let's do this what i didn't
realize when i was building this and you
can see me like going back and getting
references is how enormous this would
end up being and i don't think that i
prepared for this quite enough i made a
few mistakes and then all of a sudden
ran out of concrete be right back
[Music]
and we're back we got enough concrete
now working with the really dark color
was almost impossible you could not see
exactly where you're placing the block
but eventually through trial and error
got there in the end it looks quite cool
yeah the big issue with the big dragon
that i made it's it's actually pretty
accurate
but um that's kind of the problem
because from this angle
you can't see
at all it just it just looks like a
giant nose look look if you're down here
it's yeah look at this it's pretty
pretty much identical
this is like never talk to me or my son
ever again
yeah um so that's pretty much the issue
i have so it doesn't look as good as it
perhaps could do however from up here it
actually looks pretty decent look
that's the dragon i was actually going
for so
if i was smart what i should have really
done is just make this top half and sink
the rest into the ground just so you got
the dragon schnoz and then you've got uh
the eyes above ground so you can see
well what it is exactly because at the
moment all you see is just
just a just a dragon schnoz like that
and you can't really tell however i was
wondering you know what am i going to do
with this space it's oh i don't want to
leave this empty and so the whole dragon
bros thing hello that that's kind of
cool this is going to end up being
excellent and the more people we get
into the dragon bro team
uh i i imagine the more that this will
get built up although there is a big
problem with these mobs they're really
quite annoying now that that's out the
way i don't really know what to do
however we will be needing more dragon
heads as there are plenty of people
alive but not enough dragon heads to go
around now how do we get dragon heads
well we can either farm them from the
end wait i think that's the only way to
farm them right
killing killing the ender dragon doesn't
do anything
my head's too big for this corridor yeah
i think i have to go to the end and get
them off of the ships there however i'm
pretty sure it's been raided pretty
heavily so
i might need to wait for the end to be
redone and then we can collect the
dragon heads
to add more people to the dragon bro
squad unfortunately mumbo hasn't been on
but there's plenty of people that are
still around so what we could do is just
take a quick look
have a look around there's plenty of
people that aren't dead the only person
that's dead on the on online right now
is exci zoomer you bleed uh but we've
got false doc and b double o
all of which
have no
gray skin on so they're they're alive
so what we're gonna do oh that one's
already that one is already taken so
what we're gonna do we're gonna get
ourselves a dispenser we're gonna get
ourselves a dragon head and we're gonna
go and we're gonna go find someone now
i'm not entirely sure how easy this is
gonna be but nobody knows that we're
after them with the dragon heads so as
soon as we see someone that's just not
wearing a helmet which is very very
unlikely
maybe we'll be able to trick them as
well it's gonna be it'll be quite simple
to do i imagine people tend to do what
they're told so yeah let's try this out
so let's go and see if we can trick b
double o first
while we've got the element of surprise
i'm pretty sure we can get b dubs
all he needs to do is not be suspecting
anything and b-dubs still lives over in
hermitville the rest of us have moved
back but he's still living there
now b-dubs should be living just beyond
area 70 whoa
what on earth
ah doc's wearing a helmet i don't know
what that was i hope i didn't spoil
anything all right where is he
where is the target i feel like b-dubs
he doesn't know me so well
oh wow a diorite castle this girl's
gonna lose his mind
this guy's gonna lose his mind there he
is b-dubs okay cool cool cool right so
this is what i'm gonna do b-dubs doesn't
really know me okay he doesn't he
doesn't know my antics he doesn't know
what i'm up to
so i feel like it's super easy for him
to to be fooled by me at least for now
until this is done as soon as as soon as
i've done this he's probably going to
learn his lesson
so let's set this up really quickly all
i'm going to do
is
set up a dispenser like this i'm going
to pop the
the dragon bro head on this
and i'm going to
boom
that's all we got to do that's it
so what we're going to do is we're going
to we're going to try and get his
attention we're going to get him to come
and inspect
and i'm going to tell him i'm going to
tell him to look down that hole right oh
here he comes here he comes here he goes
he must he must be so confused utterly
utterly bamboozled do
as i do
it's important all right so i'm going to
take off my stuff i've taken off i've
taken it off i can't take off the i
can't take off the dragon helmet
come on come on beat ups do as i do do
as i do
do as i do
come on come on b-dubs you can figure it
out do as you do
come on come on b-dubs it's not that
hard look look look
no
come on he's he's he's
come on
you you're smart come on figure it out
figure it out
do as i do
come on look
yes yes
[Music]
perfect perfect perfect
now
look in this
that was so much easier than i thought
[Laughter]
yes yes dragon bros
oh my goodness
and now
what a dream come true my work here
here is done
my work here is done but you didn't do
anything
exactly
[Laughter]
oh my goodness i cannot believe that
that worked i i utterly i cannot believe
that that worked
that means
that probably means as long as the other
hermits don't catch wind of of my
of my deadly schemes
that
we can get other people into the dragon
bro squad
oh my goodness that was i can't believe
it i can't believe he fell for the look
in this dispenser
oh my goodness
right so we're gonna have to bring
b-dubs in on in our little like bunker
and stuff it's gonna be fun
i shouldn't have done that i need to be
holding one of these at all times
huh right we're gonna need some more
dragon heads
but i haven't been to the end in a while
i'm not even sure i'm equipped to go in
the end to be honest
the dragon bro squad is shaping up super
nicely so i'm gonna talk to b dubs off
camera and i'm gonna explain to him what
just happened and what it means so that
we can bring him in on in on our little
secret here and we can be dragon bros
but that is all i have time for today
but i want to say a huge huge thank you
to everyone that actually genuinely
shopped at sahara and bought a sahara
t-shirt i've got one myself and i
absolutely love it so i'm gonna do a
quick plug for my new t-shirt
in the description there is a link there
to my t-shirt store look at these look
at these t-shirts the zahara logo is
looking epic and coming up next week
we're going to have a limited edition
sahara t-shirt with a little mustache on
the cactus so more information on that
but please please please check out the
store it is officially up and running
people have been absolutely loving the
merchandise so i want to say another
huge thank you to everyone that checked
it out but i will see you in the next
episode which happens to be number
100 hello
number 100 so we're probably going to do
something a little bit different with
the first half of the video it might be
like a little bit of a retrospective and
it should be really really cool but i'm
going to try and make number 100
particularly special if i can because
i've never had a series get to 100
episodes before thank you very much for
watching and good bye
dragon bros